{
    "id": "db02861adbf94b65b69352d148524353",
    "title": "Because And Because Of",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We cancelled the trip ..................... the rain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4314c5ac64b043c2a4b3cc72b1b395c7"
        },
        {
            "question": "He sat down ………………….. he was feeling dizzy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bdab7e0b4340468295ad54ec485f20a6"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is …………………. your mother that we got into this mess.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4e088fd4ee424604adc5e5db16a59874"
        },
        {
            "question": "We hurried indoors ……………….. it was raining.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d99900271f814a50b8b008c504f9af91"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was late …………………. the traffic.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "05d02392823e4aaab8702a563437b91a"
        },
        {
            "question": "We could not reach on time ………………… the traffic was terrible.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "992bf6d5ec90433aa31ec6fb69dc76ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "The exam was easy ...................... he knew all the answers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bf57757bb33e43f0874e2d86838866b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "He can’t walk .....................… his illness.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b1c11faf3cdd49b6b5881f486e1a1c93"
        },
        {
            "question": "He lost his job ...................... the recession.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3172373c8e3e49c39096e7b4d4fce145"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. the language problem, I couldn’t win the argument.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Because of",
                "Because"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c387d987b3644079acd3ec959191f3aa"
        }
    ]
}